Bruce A. Morrison Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Legislative Assistant: Stuart Gaul, undated, 1980-1990
  - CFC's, 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 304)
  - Children, Youth and Families, 1989 (Box 13:, Folder 305-313)
  - Child support, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 314)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the people of El Salvador (CISPES), 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 315)
  - Clean air, 1987-1989 (Box 13:, Folder 316-320)
  - Clean Water, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 321)
  - Communication, 1989-1990 (Box 13:, Folder 322)
  - Computer education, 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 323)
  - Congress: general, 1987-1990 (Box 13:, Folder 324)
  - Conservation, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 325)
  - Consumer, 1986-1987 (Box 13:, Folder 326)
  - Cosponsorships, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 327)
  - Cubans, 1986-1987 (Box 13:, Folder 328-329)
  - Death penalty, 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 330)
  - Deferral Case, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 331)
  - Democrat study group on health care task force, 1989 (Box 13:, Folder 332)
  - Dial-a-porn, 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 333)
  - Disability law project, 1989 (Box 13:, Folder 334)
  - Disabled, 1989-1990 (Box 13:, Folder 335)
  - Druggists, 1987 (Box 13:, Folder 336)
  - Drug free workplace, 1988 (Box 13:, Folder 337)
  - Drug Bill, 1986-1988 (Box 14:, Folder 338-341)
  - Dores Honderz letter to NYT, 1988 (Box 14:, Folder 342)
  - East Haven Industrial park, 1987 (Box 14:, Folder 343)
  - Economic: general, 1980-1990 (Box 14:, Folder 344)
  - Education, 1987-1989 (Box 14:, Folder 345-346)
  - Eligibility management system, 1990 (Box 14:, Folder 347)
  - Energy, 1987-1989 (Box 14:, Folder 348-350)
  - English first, 1987 (Box 14:, Folder 351)
  - Environment, 1984-1989 (Box 14:, Folder 352-357)
  - Environment, 1989-1990 (Box 15:, Folder 358-359)
  - Ethanol/methanol, 1987-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 360)
  - Ethics: conflict of interest, 1986-1987 (Box 15:, Folder 361)
  - Ethics: campaign finance, 1989 (Box 15:, Folder 362)
  - Farms, 1990 (Box 15:, Folder 363)
  - Federal Insecticide, Fungicide and Rodenticide Act, 1987-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 364)
  - Fish and fisheries, 1987 (Box 15:, Folder 365)
  - Flood insurance, 1986-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 366-367)
  - Forestry service, 1989 (Box 15:, Folder 368)
  - Foster care: elderly, 1987-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 369)
  - Foster care, 1988 (Box 15:, Folder 370)
  - Full Committee markup, 1987 (Box 15:, Folder 371-372)
  - Garbage: CT, 1989 (Box 15:, Folder 373)
  - Genocide Treaty, 1987-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 374)
  - General Accounting office, 1987-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 375)
  - Government, 1986-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 376-377)
  - Gov. O'Neill: letters, 1989-1990 (Box 15:, Folder 378)
  - Grove City, 1986 (Box 15:, Folder 379)
  - Handicapped/developmental, 1987-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 380)
  - Hastings, Alcie (Judge), 1987 (Box 15:, Folder 381)
  - Hazardous waste, 1986-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 382-383)
  - Health care, 1986-1988 (Box 15:, Folder 384-385)
  - Health care, 1987-1990 (Box 16:, Folder 386-387)
  - Health care benefits: Kennedy/Waxman, 1987-1988 (Box 16:, Folder 388)
  - Health care industry, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 389)
  - Health insurance access, 1987-1990 (Box 16:, Folder 390)
  - Health maintenance organizations, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 391)
  - Historical preservation, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 392)
  - Home health care, 1985, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 393-394)
  - Hospice, 1986-1989 (Box 16:, Folder 395)
  - Hospitals, 1989 (Box 16:, Folder 396)
  - Hunger, undated (Box 16:, Folder 397)
  - Immunization, 1987-1990 (Box 16:, Folder 398)
  - Income dealing/distribution, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 399)
  - Independent council, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 400-402)
  - Independent living, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 403)
  - Independent prosecutors, 1988 (Box 16:, Folder 404-405)
  - Infant mortality, 1988 (Box 16:, Folder 406)
  - Interior, 1989-1970 (Box 16:, Folder 407)
  - Iran Contra, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 408)
  - Iroquois, 1989 (Box 16:, Folder 409)
  - Japanese American compensation: WW II, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 410)
  - Judiciary, 1987 (Box 16:, Folder 411)
  - JTPA: business/education, 1989 (Box 16:, Folder 412)
  - KGM: Harford Service, 1989 (Box 16:, Folder 413)
  - Lead in drinking water, 1988 (Box 16:, Folder 414)
  - Legislative veto, 1983-1986 (Box 16:, Folder 415)
  - Locomotive engineers, 1986-1987 (Box 16:, Folder 416)
  - Long Island Sound, 1985-1989 (Box 16:, Folder 417-420)
  - Long Island Sound, 1986-1989 (Box 17:, Folder 421-428)
  - Long Island study, 1989 (Box 17:, Folder 429)
  - Long term care, 1987-1989 (Box 17:, Folder 430-433)
  - Low income home energy assistance, 1989 (Box 17:, Folder 434-435)
  - Low level radioactive waste, 1985-1990 (Box 17:, Folder 436-437)
  - Lyme disease, 1986-1988 (Box 17:, Folder 438)
  - Mail-wire fraud, 1987 (Box 17:, Folder 439)
  - McKinney, Stewart B.: wildlife refuge, 1988-1990 (Box 17:, Folder 440-441)
  - Medicare, 1987-1990 (Box 17:, Folder 442-447)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1987-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 448)
  - Mental health, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 449-450)
  - Milford Harbor, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 451)
  - Mrazek, Bob: newsletters, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 452)
  - National Health Care, 1989-1990 (Box 18:, Folder 453-455)
  - National Alliance of Business, 1990 (Box 18:, Folder 456)
  - New Haven Harbor, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 457)
  - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 18:, Folder 458)
  - Nicaragua, 1986-1987 (Box 18:, Folder 459)
  - Northeast Utilities, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 460)
  - North Haven Mall, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 461)
  - Notch Bill, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 462)
  - Nuclear power, 1987-1989 (Box 18:, Folder 463-464)
  - Nuclear waste, 1987-1989 (Box 18:, Folder 465-466)
  - Oil spills, 1987-1989 (Box 18:, Folder 467-468)
  - Older Americans Act, 1987-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 469)
  - Original intent, 1986 (Box 18:, Folder 470)
  - OSHA, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 471)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 472)
  - Ozone, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 473-474)
  - Parental leave, 1987-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 475)
  - Pepper, Claude, 1988-1989 (Box 18:, Folder 476-479)
  - Perkins/Elmer, 1989-1990 (Box 18:, Folder 480)
  - Physicians assistants, 1989 (Box 18:, Folder 481)
  - Polygraph, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 482)
  - Private bills, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 483-484)
  - Prospective payments: Diagnosis related groups, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 485)
  - Quaddafe, Omar, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 486)
  - Radon, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 487)
  - Railroads, 1987 (Box 19:, Folder 488)
  - Recess appointments: judges, 1987 (Box 19:, Folder 489)
  - Recycling, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 490-493)
  - Religious Property Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 494)
  - Sentencing guidelines, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 495)
  - Sludge, 1988-1989 (Box 19:, Folder 496)
  - Smoking, 1986-1990 (Box 19:, Folder 497-500)
  - Social security, 1981-1990 (Box 19:, Folder 501-503)
  - Solid waste, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 504-506)
  - Special prosecutor, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 507-508)
  - Stamp, 1985-1990 (Box 19:, Folder 509-511)
  - Storms: CT, 1989 (Box 19:, Folder 512)
  - Super collider, 1987-1989 (Box 19:, Folder 513-514)
  - Superconducting super collider, 1987-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 515-516)
  - Superfund clean-up, 1986-1989 (Box 20:, Folder 517)
  - Survey instrument, 1990 (Box 20:, Folder 518)
  - Suspension of duty, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 519-520)
  - Tax exempt municipal state bonds, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 521)
  - Taxation of graduate student income, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 522)
  - Taxes, 1990 (Box 20:, Folder 523)
  - Thank-you letters, 1989-1990 (Box 20:, Folder 524)
  - Third world debt, 1985-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 525)
  - Tsongas Reform Bill, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 526)
  - Trade, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 527)
  - Transportation, 1987-1990 (Box 20:, Folder 528-530)
  - UConn Industrial Research Center, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 531)
  - Upjohn, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 532)
  - Yale, 1987-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 533)
  - Yellowstone fires, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 534)
  - Water, 1985-1989 (Box 20:, Folder 535)
  - Weir Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 20:, Folder 536)
  - Welfare, 1985-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 537-541)
  - Whales, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 542)
  - Guest books, 1983-1989 (Box 21:, Folder 543)
  - Scrap book - 2nd Int'l Parliamentary Congress, 1987 (Box 21:, Folder 544)
  - Program for Newly Elected Members of Congress: Harvard University, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 545)
- Series III: Legislative Assistant: Nora Engel, 1983-1989
  - Child obscenity/pornography, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 546)
  - Campaign finance, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 547)
  - Children, Youth and Family Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 22:, Folder 548)
  - Cochran/Discharge/Due Process, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 549)
  - Computer education, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 550)
  - Drug Bill, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 551-557)
  - Dukakis/Education, 1988 (Box 22:, Folder 558)
  - Education, 1987-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 559)
  - Education/technology: Merrifield, 1987 (Box 22:, Folder 560)
  - L'Ambiance Plaza, 1985-1989 (Box 23:, Folder 561-567)
  - Ninth Square Project, 1983-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 568)
  - Weicker: Occupational Safety and Health Act, 1987-1988 (Box 23:, Folder 569)
- Series IV: Legislative Correspondent: P. Knight Elsberry, undated, 1982-1990
  - Subseries A: Issues and Legislation, undated, 1982-1989
    - Animal patent, 1987-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 570-572)
    - BAM Reports from Washington, 1983-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 573)
    - BAM statements and speeches, 1983-1984 (Box 24:, Folder 574)
    - Bankruptcy procedure, 1987 (Box 24:, Folder 575)
    - Church Street South, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 576)
    - Coast Guard: Dick Weed, 1982-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 577)
    - Columbia Federal Recap Plan, 1988 (Box 24:, Folder 578)
    - Committee on the Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration, Refugees, and Int'l Law, 1989 (Box 24:, Folder 579)
    - Deep Draft navigation, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 580)
    - Die casting, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 581)
    - Disability Hearing, 1987 (Box 24:, Folder 582)
    - Disability Hearing: Long Island, 1987 (Box 24:, Folder 583-584)
    - District water projects, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 585)
    - Drug Bill, 1988 (Box 24:, Folder 586)
    - Education, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 587)
    - Emergency food and shelter, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 588)
    - Evans Project: Constitution Bank Corp., 1987-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 589)
    - Federal practice issues: court package, 1988 (Box 24:, Folder 590)
    - Goodman, Doug, 1988 (Box 25:, Folder 591)
    - Hartford Housing I: Sect. 202 Project, 1987 (Box 25:, Folder 592)
    - H.R. 162: high risk occupations, 1987 (Box 25:, Folder 593)
    - Industrial design legislations, 1988-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 594)
    - Iroquois natural gas pipelines, 1986-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 595-601)
    - Ivan Lendl, 1987-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 602-604)
    - McCarran-Ferguson, 1987-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 605-607)
    - Morrison news releases and general legislation, 1989 (Box 26:, Folder 608-609)
    - North New Haven Industrial Center, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 610)
    - Paul Reed: pension issues, 1985 (Box 26:, Folder 611)
    - Photos: Bruce Morrison/Michelle Perrault, undated (Box 26:, Folder 612)
    - Photos, 1988 (Box 26:, Folder 613-614)
    - Price-Anderson, 1986-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 615-618)
    - Science Park, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 619)
    - Roger Sherman, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 620)
    - Spectrum file, 1986 (Box 26:, Folder 621)
    - Union Local 559, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 622)
    - University of Baltimore Law School, 1989 (Box 26:, Folder 623)
    - Video Library Privacy Protection Act, 1988 (Box 26:, Folder 624)
    - Virgin Islands, 1986-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 625-626)
    - West Haven Housing Authority, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 627)
    - Wire rope issue, 1983-1985 (Box 26:, Folder 628)
    - You and Your Success Module, 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 629)
  - Subseries B: Robos Letters, 1983-1990
    - Art/defense/arms control/education/civil rights/commerce/communications/crime/alcohol and drugs/CYF welfare, 1983-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 630)
    - Energy/environment, 1983-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 631)
    - Federal employees/foreign affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 632)
    - Foreign affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 633)
    - Gun control/health/housing, 1984-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 634)
    - Immigration/insurance/judiciary, 1983-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 635)
    - Labor/medicare, 1985-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 636)
    - Office/recommendations/endorsements/social security/political, 1984-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 637)
    - Taxes, 1983-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 638-639)
    - Trade, 1984-1986 (Box 27:, Folder 640)
    - Transportation/veterans, 1983-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 641)
    - Animal rights/banking/children, youth, family, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 642)
    - Civil rights/commerce/education/federal employees, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 643)
    - Federal employees/foreign affairs/government affairs/ housing/immigration/judiciary/labor, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 644)
    - Trade/veterans/welfare/women's issues, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 645)
    - Agriculture/animal rights/aging/banking budget, 1984-1987 (Box 28:, Folder 646)
    - Budget, 1984-1987 (Box 28:, Folder 647)
    - Health/insurance/interior/medicare/office/science and technology/social security/state issues/taxes/transportation/workers' comp./railroad retirement/post office/banking/commerce/communications, 1983-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 648)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 28:, Folder 649)
    - Labor, 1985-89 (Box 28:, Folder 650)
    - Federal employees/postal service/trade, 1985-89 (Box 28:, Folder 651)
    - Aging/alcohol and drugs/agriculture/arms control/arts/budget/commemorative legislation, 1985-89 (Box 28:, Folder 652)
    - Ethics/government affairs/arms control/defense/Latin America, 1989 (Box 28:, Folder 653)
    - Animal rights/child care/drugs/education/environment, 1990 (Box 28:, Folder 654)
    - Family/health/medicare/social security/transportation, 1990 (Box 28:, Folder 655)
    - Communications/crime/defense/disabled/energy/environment/gun control, 1988-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 656)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 28:, Folder 657)
    - Current Code Volume Report: by category, 1985 (Box 28:, Folder 658)
  - Subseries C: KB Letter Subject Headings, 1983-1990
    - Federal Gevernment/health and welfare/judiciary/labor/postal/taxes/science/transportation/veterans/women's, 1983-1984 (Box 29:, Folder 659)
    - Aging/arts/agriculture/banking/children/commerce/communication/congress/education/energy, 1984 (Box 29:, Folder 660)
    - Foreign aid/veterans/women/immigration/civil/arts/housing, 1989-1990 (Box 29:, Folder 661)
    - KB entry numbers
      - 127-526 (Box 29:, Folder 662)
      - 529-1876 (Box 29:, Folder 663)
      - 1897-2248 (Box 29:, Folder 664)
      - 2251-3043 (Box 29:, Folder 665)
      - 3044-3373 (Box 29:, Folder 666)
      - 3374-3674 (Box 29:, Folder 667)
      - 3675-3923 (Box 29:, Folder 668)
      - 3924-4635 (Box 29:, Folder 669)
      - 4656-5369 (Box 29:, Folder 670)
      - 5371-5836 (Box 29:, Folder 671)
      - 5837-6573 (Box 29:, Folder 672)
      - 6579-7288 (Box 29:, Folder 673)
    - Agriculture (Box 30:, Folder 674)
    - Alcohol and drugs (Box 30:, Folder 675)
    - Animal rights (Box 30:, Folder 676)
    - Banking (Box 30:, Folder 677)
    - Budget (Box 30:, Folder 678)
    - Business (Box 30:, Folder 679)
    - Children, family, and youth (Box 30:, Folder 680)
    - Civil rights (Box 30:, Folder 681)
    - Civil liberties (Box 30:, Folder 682)
    - Commemorative legislation (Box 30:, Folder 683)
    - Commerce (Box 30:, Folder 684)
    - Communications (Box 30:, Folder 685)
    - Crime (Box 30:, Folder 686)
    - Defense and arms control (Box 30:, Folder 687)
    - Disabled (Box 30:, Folder 688)
    - Education (Box 30:, Folder 689)
    - Energy (Box 30:, Folder 690)
    - Environment (Box 30:, Folder 691)
    - Foreign affairs (Box 30:, Folder 692)
    - Government affairs and congress (Box 30:, Folder 693)
    - Health (Box 30:, Folder 694)
    - Human rights (Box 30:, Folder 695)
    - Housing (Box 30:, Folder 696)
    - Immigration (Box 30:, Folder 697)
    - Information request (Box 30:, Folder 698)
    - Insurance (Box 30:, Folder 699)
    - Judiciary (Box 30:, Folder 700)
    - Labor and federal employees (Box 30:, Folder 701)
    - Latin America (Box 30:, Folder 702)
    - Medicare information (Box 30:, Folder 703-704)
    - Middle East (Box 30:, Folder 705)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30:, Folder 706)
    - Pension (Box 30:, Folder 707)
    - Postal service (Box 30:, Folder 708)
    - Retirement (Box 30:, Folder 709)
    - Science technology (Box 30:, Folder 710)
    - Social Security (Box 30:, Folder 711)
    - Assorted statements (Box 30:, Folder 712)
    - Tax (Box 30:, Folder 713)
    - Trade (Box 30:, Folder 714)
    - Transportation/aviation (Box 30:, Folder 715)
    - Veteran (Box 30:, Folder 716)
    - Welfare reform (Box 30:, Folder 717)
    - Women's rights/abortion (Box 30:, Folder 718)
    - Press clippings (Box 30:, Folder 719)
    - Press clippings, 1987 (Box 31:, Folder 720-725)
    - Congressional records, 1987 (Box 31:, Folder 726)
    - Housing news clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 727)
    - Press clippings, 1987-1990 (Box 31:, Folder 728)
    - Press clippings, 1988 (Box 31:, Folder 729-740)
    - Press clippings, 1989 (Box 31:, Folder 741-51)
    - Press clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 752)
    - Undated articles (Box 32:, Folder 753)
- Series V: Legislative Correspondence, 1983-1990
  - 1983 January - August (microfiche) (Box 33)
  - 1983 August - December (Box 34)
  - 1984 January - April (Box 35)
  - 1984 May - October (Box 36)
  - 1984 October - 1985 March (Box 37)
  - 1985 March - May (Box 38)
  - 1985 May - July (Box 39)
  - 1985 July - October (Box 40)
  - 1985 October - December (Box 41)
  - 1985-1986 (citizen action cards) (Box 42)
  - 1986 January - March (Box 43)
  - 1986 March - June (Box 44)
  - 1986 June - September (Box 45)
  - 1986 September - December (Box 46)
  - 1987 January - March (Box 47)
  - 1987 March - May (Box 48)
  - 1987 June - September (Box 49)
  - 1987 September - December (Box 50)
  - 1988 January - March (Box 51)
  - 1988 March - June (Box 52)
  - 1988 June - Septmber (Box 53)
  - 1988 September - December (Box 54)
  - 1989 January - February (Box 55)
  - 1989 March - April (Box 56)
  - 1989 May - June (Box 57)
  - 1989 June - August (Box 58)
  - 1989 September - October (Box 59)
  - 1989 October - December (Box 60)
  - 1987 November - 1989 July (file #245-275) (Box 61)
  - 1989 May - 1990 December (file # 275-300) (Box 62)
  - 1990 January - May (file #290-297) (Box 63)
  - 1990 January - November (Box 64)
  - 1990 March - April (Box 65)
  - 1990 April - October (Box 66)
  - 1990 June - July (Box 67)
  - 1990 August - September (Box 68)
  - 1990 September - November (Box 69)
  - 1990 January - December (Citizen Action Cards) (Box 70)
  - 1990 January - December (Citizen Action Cards) (Box 71)
- Series VI: 1994 Addition
  - (Box 72-74)
- Series VII: 2000 Addition
  - Morrison Speeches and Articles (Box 75, 88)
    - Federal Housing Finance Board, 1995-2000
  - Federal Housing Finance Board Chairmanship
    - Congressional Correspondence (Box 75, 76)
    - FHLB System and FHFB News Coverage, 1995-2000
  - 1990 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 77, 83)
    - Taxes, O'Neill Clips, Weicker Clips
    - Rowland Clips
  - Congressional Papers (Box 78)
    - Articles and Clips, Congressional Quarterly, 1978-1990
    - John Rowland Finance Materials, 1980-1988
  - Irish Peace Process Chronological Files, 1997-2000 (Box 79)
  - Irish Human Rights Files
  - Irish Equality Issues
  - Irish Trips:
    - Pittsburgh, 1996 September
    - San Francisco, 1996 November
  - Irish Material from Tom Hayden
  - Irish Peace Process (chronological files), 1995-1997 (Box 80)
  - Irish-American Unity Conference, 1996
  - Voting Record (Box 81-82)
    - 100th Congress
    - 101st Congress
    - 98th Congress, 2nd Session
    - 99th Congress
    - 98th Congress, CQ Press
  - 98th Congress—Sponsorships/Cosponsorships
  - 101st Congress—Cosponsorships
  - Morrison Visa Press Materials
    - Press, 1991, 1993
    - Press Reports, 1992
  - 1990 Gubernatorial Campaign Materials (Box 84)
  - 1990 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 85)
    - Communications Notebook
    - Campaign Contributions, 1990
  - 3rd District Legislative Profile, 1987-1988
  - Commission on Immigration Reform, 1992-1999 (Box 86, 96)
  - Audio: (Box 89)
    - Today with PK, 1999; (2 copies)
    - America and the World, 1994
    - Americans and the Great Irish Famine
  - Video:
    - The Road to Bright City, 1993
    - Out of Ireland
    - Bruce Morrison: This is Your Life Banquet, 1982
    - Ireland on the Move
    - Niall O'Dowd “An Irish Voice”, 1998
    - Washington Watch, 1994
    - The Road to Peace
    - Law & Order Episode—Niall O'Dowd
    - FHFB Chairman Morrison swearing in, 1995
    - Morrison for Governor, (2 copies)
    - 726 Express, 1996
    - A Leap of Faith
    - U.S. Delegation Visit to Conway Mill, 1993
    - Bloomberg Forum Interview, 1996
    - CBS News
      - Before Your Eyes
      - Don't Take My Daddy
    - University of Limerick Presidential Inauguration, 1998
    - RTE Interview
    - BBC Belfast Jim Dougal Interview, 1996
    - ITN Interview, 1995
    - Ellis Island Medal of Honor Induction, 1996
    - Brian O'Swyer Interview with Sam Roberts
    - McNeill Lehrer Interview on Immigration
    - Journey for Peace, Clinton to Ireland, 1995
    - The San Patricios—St. Patrick's Battalion
    - Home Away from Home—Yanks in Ireland
    - CBS News Nightwatch, 1991
    - Morrison for Governor—rough cut, 1990
    - South Shore Bank “Borrowing Among Minorities”
  - Americans for a New Irish Agenda (Box 90)
    - Formation and Constitution, 1993
    - White House Meeting, 1994
    - Special Envoy to Northern Ireland Materials
    - Agendas and Minutes
    - Miscellaneous
  - Irish Fact Finding Mission, 1993
    - Background
    - Current
  - Irish Transition Meeting, 1993
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1993
  - Opsahl Commission
  - BAM Letter to Hillary R. Clinton urging Senate Run, 1999
  - Irish Files, 1993-1994 (Box 91)
  - Irish Affairs Press
  - ANIA—Irish Americans for Clinton-Gore, 1996
  - Clinton Fundraiser
  - 1982 Congressional Campaign (Box 92)
    - Literature
    - Clips
    - Press Releases
    - Polling
    - Administrative
    - Miscellaneous
  - 1988 Congressional Campaign Materials (Box 93)
  - 1984 Congressional Relection Campaign materials (Box 94)
  - 1986 Congressional Media Strategies, data, etc.
  - Congressional Papers (Box 95)
    - CQ Clips
    - Scorecard Summaries
      - Environment
      - International
      - Religious
      - Family
      - Civil Rights
      - Senior Citizens
      - Women
      - Business
      - Education
      - Agriculture
      - Veterans
      - Urban
      - Citizens Groups
      - Unions
      - Miscellaneous
      - Taxes
  - 1990 Campaign Clips—Morrison and O'Neill
  - Congressional and Gubernatorial Campaigns, 1982-1990 (Box 97)
    - Audio and Video Tapes of speeches, meetings
  - Individual Files (Box 98)
    - All Party Talks
    - Irish Prisoners—Extradition
    - Irish Immigration
    - Chuck Boyle Correspondence
    - Monica McWilliams Materials
    - Jean Kennedy Smith
    - Mary Boergers Materials
    - United Technologies Dublin Plant
    - Habitat for Humanity, Belfast
    - Joe Carroll Article, 1997
    - American Ireland Fund
    - Generic Peace Process Files
    - Committee on the Administration of Justice (Jane Winter/Martin O'Brien)
    - British Irish Rights Watch materials
    - Good Friday Agreement
    - Larry Butler, White House
    - Mo Mowlam, British Parliament
    - Scottish National Party
    - Hartford Courant Article, 1997
    - Hartford Courant Article, 1998
    - Washington Post Letter, 2000
    - IADL
    - Gore Immigration Letter, 1996
    - E.J. Dionne
    - Letter to Clinton, 1998, 2000
    - Irish Travel Information